[Section]
Name = Abyss Web server X1
Version = 2.12.1 build 190530
License = Freeware
Description = Enables you to host your Web sites on your computer. It supports secure SSL/TLS connections (HTTPS) as well as a wide range of Web technologies. It can also run advanced PHP, Perl, Python, ASP, ASP.NET, and Ruby on Rails Web applications, which can be backed by databases such as MySQL, SQLite, MS SQL Server, MS Access, or Oracle.
Size = 2.4 MiB
Category = 5
URLSite = http://www.aprelium.com/
URLDownload = http://www.aprelium.com/data/abwsx1.exe
SHA1 = df5e52bb6057ee454587d46a8469f0f40cf32282
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 2508088

[Section.0407]
Description = Ermöglicht es Webseiten auf Ihrem Computer zu hosten. Er unterstützt sichere SSL/TLS Verbindungen (HTTPS) sowie eine Vielfalt an Web Technologien. Er kann ebenfalls PHP, Perl, Python, ASP, ASP.NET, und Ruby on Rails Web Anwendungen ausführen, welche von Datenbanken, wie MySQL, SQLite, MS SQL Server, MS Access, oder Oracle unterstützt werden können.
Size = 2,4 MiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Permite alojar sitios Web localmente en el equipo. Soporta conexiones seguras SSL / TLS (HTTPS) así como una gran cantidad de tecnologías web. También puede ejecutar aplicaciones web en PHP, Perl, Python, ASP, ASP.Net, Ruby y Ruby on Rails, que pueden ser asociadas con bases de datos tales como MySQL, SQLite, MS SQL Server, MS Access u Oracle.

[Section.040c]
Description = Abyss Web Server vous permet d'héberger vos sites internet sur votre ordinateur. Il supporte les connexions sécurisées SSL/TLS (HTTPS) ainsi qu'un grand nombre de technologies web. Il peut également faire tourner des applications web PHP, Perl, Python, ASP, ASP.Net, Ruby et Ruby on Rails, qui peuvent être associées à des bases de données telles que MySQL, SQLite, MS SQL Server, MS Access ou Oracle.
Size = 2,4 Mio

[Section.10]
Description = Abyss Web Server consente di ospitare i vostri siti Web sul computer. Supporta connessioni sicure SSL / TLS (HTTPS), così come una vasta gamma di tecnologie web. E' inoltre possibile eseguire avanzato PHP, Perl, Python, ASP, ASP.NET, e Ruby on Rails, applicazioni Web che possono essere supportate da database come MySQL, SQLite, MS SQL Server, MS Access, o Oracle.

[Section.0413]
Description = Abyss Web Server staat u toe om websites aan te bieden op uw computer. Het ondersteunt beveiligde SSL/TLS verbindingen (HTTPS) en ook een breed gamma aan andere Web technologieën. Het kan ook gevorderde PHP, Perl, Python, ASP, ASP.NET en Ruby on Rails Web applicaties uitvoeren, die kunnen ondersteund zijn door databanken zoals MySQL, SQLite, MS SQL Server, MS Access or Oracle.

[Section.0415]
Description = Abyss Web Server pozwala Ci na stworzenie serwera WWW na własnym komputerze. Ten program obsługuje zabezpieczone połączenia typu SSL/TLS (HTTPS) i wiele technologii Sieci. Może także uruchamiać zaawansowane aplikacje internetowe takie jak PHP, Perl, Python, ASP, ASP.NET, i Ruby on Rails. Mogą one zostać oparte o MySQL, SQLite, MS SQL Server, MS Access, lub Oracle.

[Section.0418]
License = Gratuită
Description = Program pentru găzduirea de situri web. Oferă conexiuni securizate SSL/TLS (HTTPS) și multe alte tehnologii Web. Poate executa aplicații Web avansate în PHP, Perl, Python, ASP, ASP.NET și Ruby on Rails, ce legături la diverse baze de date externe.
Size = 2,4 Mio

[Section.0419]
Description = Позволит разместить веб-сайты на вашем компьютере. Он поддерживает защищенные SSL/TLS-соединения (протокол https), а также широкий спектр веб-технологий. Он также может запустить веб-приложения PHP, Perl, Python, ASP, ASP.NET и Ruby, которые, могут быть связаны с базами данных MySQL, SQLite, MS SQL Server, MS Access или Oracle.
Size = 2,4 МиБ

[Section.041f]
Name = Abyss Umûmî Ağ Sunucusu X1
License = Ücretsiz
Description = Bilgisayarınızda ağ sitelerinizin barındırılmasına olanak sağlar. Ağ teknolojilerilerinin bir geniş yelpâzesiyle birlikte güvenli SSL/TLS bağlantılarını (HTTPS) destekler. Ayrıca MySQL, SQLite, MS SQL Server, MS Access ve Oracle gibi veri tabanlarıyla desteklenebilen gelişmiş PHP, Perl, Python, ASP, ASP.NET ve Rails üzerinde Ruby ağ uygulamalarını çalıştırabilir.
Size = 2,4 MiB

[Section.0422]
Description = Abyss Web Server дозволить вам утримувати веб-сайти на вашому комп'ютері. Від підтримує безпечні SSL/TLS з'єднання (HTTPS) та великий ряд веб-технологій. Він також запускає PHP, Perl, Python, ASP, ASP.NET, та Ruby on Rails веб-додатки, які можуть підтримуватись такими базами даних, як MySQL, SQLite, MS SQL Server, MS Access, чи Oracle.

[Section.0425]
Description = Lubab hostida veebilehti arvutis. Toetab SSL/TLS ühendusi (HTTPS) ja lai valik veebitehnoloogiaid. See saab veel rakendada arenenud PHP, Perl, Python, ASP, ASP.NET ja Ruby on Rails veebirakendusi, mida saab tagada andmebaasidega nagu MySQL, SQLite, MS SQL Server, MS Access või Oracle.
License = Vabavaraline
Size = 2,4 MiB

[Section.0804]
License = 免费软件
Description = 使您能够在您的计算机上搭建网站。它支持安全 SSL/TLS 连接（HTTPS）以及相当多的网络技术。它也可以运行由诸如 MySQL, SQLite, MS SQL Server, MS Access 或 Oracle 之类的数据库提供支持的 PHP, Perl, Python, ASP, ASP.NET, 及 Ruby on Rails 的网络程序。

[Section.0813]
Description = Abyss Web Server staat u toe om websites aan te bieden op uw computer. Het ondersteunt beveiligde SSL/TLS verbindingen (HTTPS) en ook een breed gamma aan andere Web technologieën. Het kan ook gevorderde PHP, Perl, Python, ASP, ASP.NET en Ruby on Rails Web applicaties uitvoeren, die kunnen ondersteund zijn door databanken zoals MySQL, SQLite, MS SQL Server, MS Access or Oracle.

