[Section]
Name = DosBlaster
Version = 2.5
License = GPL
Description = A shell extension which makes it possible to open any DOS executable in DOSBox via right click. This version contains DOSBox 0.70, but can be simply updated by installing a newer DOSBox into the DosBlaster folders.
Size = 2.1 MiB
Category = 16
URLSite = http://dosblaster.sourceforge.net/
URLDownload = http://download.sourceforge.net/project/dosblaster/DosBlaster%202.5%20%28x86%29/Downloads/DosbasterSetup_2_5.exe
SHA1 = 900927b51b67e09d83d924670e0ca72ba8151901
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 2152137

[Section.0407]
Description = Shell Extension, die es ermöglicht jede DOS Anwendung via Rechtsklick in DOSBox zu öffnen. Diese Version beinhaltet DOSBox 0.70, kann aber sehr einfach aktualisiert werden, indem man ein neueres DOSBox in die DosBlaster Ordner installiert.
Size = 2,1 MiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Una extensión del explorador de archivos que permite abrir cualquier ejecutable DOS en DOSBox haciendo clic derecho del ratón. Esta versión contiene DOSBox 0.70, pero se puede actualizar fácilmente instalando una nueva versión de DOSBox en la carpeta de DosBlaster.

[Section.040c]
Description = DosBlaster est une extension Shell qui permet d'ouvrir n'importe quel exécutable DOS dans DOSBox via un click droit. Cette version contient DOSBox 0.70 mais peut être simplement mise à jour en installant une nouvelle version de DOSBox dans les répertoires de DosBlaster.
Size = 2,1 Mio

[Section.10]
Description = DosBlaster è un'estensione della shell, consente di aprire qualsiasi file DOS eseguibile in DOSBox tramite un clic del tasto destro. Questa versione contiene DOSBox 0,70, ma può essere aggiornato semplicemente installando una nuova versione di DOSBox nella directory DosBlaster.

[Section.0413]
Description = DosBlaster is een Shell uitbreiding dat het mogelijk maakt om een DOS executable in DOSBox te openen via een rechterklik. Deze versie bevat DOSBox 0.70, maar kan eenvoudig worden geupdatet door een recentere versie van DOSBox te installeren in de DosBlaster mappen.

[Section.0415]
Description = DosBlaster to rozszerzenie powłoki, które umożliwia otwarcie każdego DOS-owego pliku wykonywalnego w DOSBox za pomocą prawego klawisza myszki. Ta wersja zawiera DosBox 0.70, ale można go łatwo zaktualizować, instalując nowszą wersje DOSBox do folderów DosBlaster.

[Section.0418]
Description = Extensie a interfeței de utilizator a sistemului, cu posibilitatea lansării de programe DOS prin clic dreapta. Această versiune conține DOSBox 0.70, însă poate fi actualizată instalând în dosarele DosBlaster o versiune mai nouă de DOSBox.
Size = 2,1 Mio

[Section.0419]
Description = Расширение оболочки, которое позволяет открыть любую DOS программу в DOSBox. Эта версия содержит DOSBox  0.70, но её можно обновить, установив новую версию DOSBox в папку DosBlaster.
Size = 2,1 МиБ

[Section.0425]
Description = Kestalaiendus, mis lubab avada igat DOS rakendust DOSBoxis parema klõpsuga. See versioon sisaldab DOSBox 0.70-i, aga saab kergelt uuendada installeerides uuema DOSBoxi DosBlaster kaustadesse.
Size = 2,1 MiB

[Section.041f]
Description = Bir DOS uygulamasını DOSBox'ta sağ tıklamayla açtırılabilmesini olanaklı duruma getiren bir kabuk uzantısıdır. Bu sürüm DOSBox 0.70 içerir ancak daha yeni bir DOSBox'u DosBlaster dizinlerinin içine kurarak kolayca günceleştirilebilir.
Size = 2,1 MiB

[Section.0422]
Description = DosBlaster це розширення оболонки, яке дозволяє запустити будь-який виконавчий файл DOS в DOSBox через правий клік. Ця версія містить DOSBox 0.70, але може бути оновлена встановленням новішої версії DOSBox в теки DosBlaster.

[Section.0804]
Description = 一个能够通过右键使任意 DOS 程序运行在 DOSBox 中的外壳拓展。这个版本包含 DOSBox 0.70，但是可以简单通过在 DosBlaster 文件夹中安装新版 DOSBox 来升级。

[Section.0813]
Description = DosBlaster is een Shell uitbreiding dat het mogelijk maakt om een DOS executable in DOSBox te openen via een rechterklik. Deze versie bevat DOSBox 0.70, maar kan eenvoudig worden geupdatet door een recentere versie van DOSBox te installeren in de DosBlaster mappen.

