[Section]
Name = Double Commander
Version = 0.8.2 beta
License = GPL
Description = An open source file manager with two panels side by side. You will need a tool like 7-Zip to extract it.
Size = 6.3 MiB
Category = 12
URLSite = http://doublecmd.sourceforge.net/
URLDownload = https://sourceforge.net/projects/doublecmd/files/DC%20for%20Windows%2032%20bit/Double%20Commander%200.8.2%20beta/doublecmd-0.8.2.i386-win32.exe
SHA1 = 3fa65b99368bbd4d20aee2743e346b3e914e3315
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 6566228

[Section.0407]
Description = Quelloffener Dateimanager mit zwei nebeneinander liegenden Panels. Zum extrahieren wird 7-Zip oder ein ähnliches Tool benötigt.
Size = 6,3 MiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Un explorador de archivos multipanel de código abierto. Es necesario utilizar 7-Zip u otro programa alternativo para extraerlo.

[Section.10]
Description = Double Commander è un open-source file-manager con due pannelli laterali affiancati. Utilizzare 7-Zip o un'utility simile per estrarlo.

[Section.0413]
Description = Double Commander is een open-bron file-manager met twee panelen zij-aan-zij. Gebruik 7-Zip of een gelijkaardige applicatie om het uit te pakken.

[Section.0415]
Description = Double Commander to menedżer plików, o otwartym źródle, z klasycznym układem dwóch paneli obok siebie. Do rozpakowania archiwum potrzebny jest 7-zip lub podobny program.

[Section.0418]
Description = Gestionar (cu surse deschise) de fișiere după modelul paneluri-alăturate. Este necesar un utilitar ca 7-Zip pentru a-l putea extrage.
Size = 6,3 Mio

[Section.0419]
Description = Double Commander - это открытый двухпанельный файловый менеджер. Вам нужен 7-Zip или подобная утилита для его распаковки.
Size = 6,3 МиБ

[Section.041f]
Description = Yan yana iki bölmeli bir açık kaynak dosya yöneticisidir. Çıkartmak için 7-Zip gibi bir araca gereksinim duyacaksınız.
Size = 6,3 MiB

[Section.0422]
Description = Double Commander - це відкритий двопанельний файловий менеджер. Вам потрібен 7-Zip або подібна утиліта щоб розпакувати його.

[Section.0425]
Description = Avatud lähtekoodiga failihaldur kahe kõrvuti oleva paneeliga. Tööriista nagu 7-zip on vaja selle lahti pakkimiseks.
Size = 6,3 MiB

[Section.0804]
Description = 含有两个面板并排的开放源码文件管理器。您将需要一个像 7-ZIP 文件的解压工具来解压它。

[Section.0813]
Description = Double Commander is een open-bron file-manager met twee panelen zij-aan-zij. Gebruik 7-Zip of een gelijkaardige applicatie om het uit te pakken.

