[Section]
Name = DVD Write Now
Version = 1.5.12 SP2
License = Freeware
Description = A free direct CD/DVD recording software. Once installed, you can use your CD/DVD RW as USB Flash or removable hard drives. Along with this you can write to CD/DVD RW recorded with UDF filesystem. You can also read UDF disks created with other software (Microsoft DVD−ROMs, RW disks recorded with Ahead InCD). You need a ZIP decompression program to install it.
Size = 1.3 MiB
Category = 12
URLSite = http://dwn.alter.org.ua/
URLDownload = https://web.archive.org/web/20150606193303if_/http://dwn.alter.org.ua/downloads/dwn_1_5_12_sp2.zip
SHA1 = 52ff824dc8363e4e6323f3417dbd337cb21d7f98
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 1354393

[Section.0407]
Description = Kostenlose CD/DVD Brennsoftware. Sobald es installiert ist, kann man CD/DVD RW als USB Flash oder Wechseldatenträger beschreiben. Auch kann man hiermit auf CD/DVD RW schreiben, welche mit dem UDF Dateisystem beschrieben wurden. Auch kann man mit dieser Software UDF Disks, welche mit anderer Software erstellt wurden, lesen. (Microsoft DVD−ROMs, RW Disks erstellt mit Ahead InCD). Es wird für die Installation ein ZIP Dekomprimierprogramm benötigt.
Size = 1,3 MiB

[Section.0a]
License = Gratuito
Description = Un programa gratuito de grabación de CD/DVD. Una vez instalado, es posible utilizar CD/DVDs regrabables como memorias flash o discos duros extraíbles. Aparte, también permite escribir CD/DVDs regrabables que utilicen el sistema de archivos UDF. Además permite leer discos creados con otros programas(DVD−ROMs de Microsoft, discos regrabables hechos con Ahead InCD). Para instalarlo es necesario utilizar un extractor ZIP.

[Section.10]
Description = Un software di masterizzazione CD/DVD diretto e gratuito. Una volta installato, è possibile utilizzare il CD/DVD RW da flash USB o dischi rigidi rimovibili. Insieme a questo è possibile scrivere CD/DVD RW registrati con filesystem UDF. È anche possibile leggere i dischi UDF creati con altri software. (Microsoft DVD-ROM, dischi RW registrati con InCD Ahead). Il programma ha bisogno di un programma di decompressione ZIP per installarlo.

[Section.0415]
Description = Darmowe oprogramowanie do nagrywania CD/DVD. Po zainstalowaniu, możesz używać płyty CD RW i DVD RW tak, jak dyski przenośne / pendrive. Możesz także zapisywać (i odczytywać dyski utworzone przez inne programy) dane do dysków RW zapisanych w systemie UDF. Wymaga programu archiwizującego do wypakowania i instalacji.

[Section.0418]
License = Gratuită
Description = Program de înscriere CD/DVD directă. Odată instalat, puteți utiliza CD/DVD ca memorie USB sau disc dur detașabil. Pe lângă aceasta, veți putea scrie pe CD/DVD inscripționate cu sistem de fișiere UDF. Se pot de asemenea citi discuri UDF create cu alte programe. (Microsoft DVD-ROM, discuri RW inscripționate cu Ahead InCD). Este necesar un program de decompresie ZIP pentru a-l instala.
Size = 1,3 Mio

[Section.0419]
Description = DVD Write Now - бесплатная программа для прямой записи на CD и DVD диски. Позволяет использовать перезаписываемые CD и DVD диски как USB-Flash или съемные жесткие диски, записывать файлы на перезаписываемые CD/DVD диски, созданные в формате UDF, и читать UDF-диски, созданные другими программами.
URLSite = http://dwn.alter.org.ua/ru/
Size = 1,3 МиБ

[Section.041f]
License = Ücretsiz
Description = Ücretsiz bir doğrudan CD/DVD saklayıcı yazılımı. Kurulduktan sonra CD/DVD RW'lerinizi, USB Flash veyâ çıkarılabilir sâbit disk sürücüleri olarak kullanabilirsiniz. Bununla birlikte UDF dosya sistemiyle saklanmış CD/DVD RW'lere yazabilirsiniz. Ayrıca Microsoft DVD−ROM'ları, Ahead InCD ile saklanmış RW diskleri gibi başka yazılımlarla oluşturulmuş UDF diskleri okuyabilirsiniz. Kurmak için bir ZIP çıkartma programı gerekir.
Size = 1,3 MiB

[Section.0425]
License = Vabavaraline
Description = Tasuta otsene CD/DVD salvestus tarkvara. Installituna saab kasutada CD/DVD RW kui USB mälupulga või irdkettana. Peale selle saab ka kirjutada CD/DVD RW-le kirjutatud UDF failisüsteemile. Saab ka lugeda UDF kettaid loodud muu tarkvaraga (Microsofti DVD-ROMid, RW kettad savlestatud Ahead InCD-ga). ZIP arhiivi dekompressiooni programmi on vaja selle installimiseks. 
Size = 1,3 MiB

[Section.0804]
License = 免费软件
Description = 免费的 CD/DVD 直接刻录软件。安装后，您可以将 CD/DVD RW 作为 U 盘或移动硬盘来使用。使用这个工具您也可以将 CD/DVD RW 烧写上 UDF 文件系统。您也可以读取其他软件（如 Microsoft DVD−ROMs, 刻录有 Ahead InCD 的 RW 光盘）创建的 UDF 光盘。您将需要一个 ZIP 解压缩程序来安装它。

