[Section]
Name = GIMP
Version = 2.8.22
License = GPL
Description = An acronym for GNU Image Manipulation Program. It is a freely distributed program for such tasks as photo retouching, image composition and image authoring.
Size = 85.4 MiB
Category = 3
URLSite = http://www.gimp.org/
URLDownload = https://download.gimp.org/pub/gimp/v2.8/windows/gimp-2.8.22-setup.exe
SHA1 = cf6fa10746a056ac728a83bd0121b83d645423de
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 89579672

[Section.0407]
Description = Akronym für GNU Image Manipulation Program. Es ist ein frei verfügbares Programm für Aufgaben wie Foto-Retusche, Bildkomposition und Bild-Authoring.
Size = 85,4 MiB

[Section.0415]
Description = Skrót od GNU Image Manipulation Program. Jest to darmowy program do tworzenia i edycji grafiki.

[Section.0418]
Description = Acronim pentru „GNU Image Manipulation Program” (program GNU de manipulare a imaginilor). Este un program gratuit pentru retușare foto, compoziție de imagine și creare de imagini.
Size = 85,4 Mio

[Section.0419]
Description = Программа для создания и обработки растровой графики. Имеется частичная поддержка работы с векторной графикой.
Size = 85,4 МиБ

[Section.041f]
Description = "GNU Image Manipulation Program" için bir kısaltma. Fotoğraf düzeltme, resim birleştirme ve resim oluşturma gibi görevler için özgürce dağıtılan bir programdır.
Size = 85,4 MiB

[Section.0425]
Description = Lühend "GNU Image Manipulation Progamm" jaoks. Tasuta jagatud programm ülesannete jaoks nagu foto viimistlus, pildikompositsioonimine, pildi loomine.
Size = 85,4 MiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Es un acrónimo en inglés de «Programa de Manipulación de Imágenes GNU». Se distribuye libremente y está pensado para el retoque fotográfico, composición de imágenes y dibujo.

[Section.0804]
Description = “GNU 图片编辑程序”的首字母缩写。它是一个用于譬如照片修描、图像构图和设计的自由软件。

[Section.10]
Description = Acronimo di GNU Image Manipulation Program. È un programma distribuito gratuitamente per attività come ritocco fotografico, composizione di immagini e creazione di immagini.

