[Section]
Name = GnuCash
Version = 2.6.21
License = GPL
Description = A personal and small-business financial-accounting software, freely licensed under the GNU GPL and available for GNU/Linux, BSD, Solaris, Mac OS X and Microsoft Windows.
Size = 114.0 MiB
Category = 10
URLSite = http://gnucash.org/
URLDownload = https://download.sourceforge.net/sourceforge/gnucash/gnucash%20%28stable%29/2.6.21/gnucash-2.6.21-setup.exe
SHA1 = 1e0c6b54de65824b24feb30e96de2f062bb9787e
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 119588469

[Section.0407]
Description = Privat und Small-Business Finanzbuchhaltungssoftware, unter der GNU GPL lizenziert und frei für GNU / Linux, BSD, Solaris, Mac OS X und Microsoft Windows verfügbar.
Size = 114,0 MiB

[Section.0415]
Description = Oprogramowanie do księgowości dla użytkowników domowych i małych firm, swobodnie licencjonowane na GNU GPL i dostępne dla systemów GNU/Linux, BSD, Solaris, Mac OS X i Microsoft Windows.

[Section.0418]
Description = Program de contabilitate financiară pentru uz personal și întreprinderi mici, oferit sub licența gratuită GNU GPL. Este disponibil pentru GNU/Linux, BSD, Solaris, Mac OS X și Windows.
Size = 114,0 Mio

[Section.0419]
Description = Программа финансового учёта. Существуют версии для GNU/Linux, BSD, Solaris, Mac OS X и Microsoft Windows.
Size = 114,0 МиБ

[Section.041f]
Description = GNU GPL altında özgürce ruhsatlanmış, GNU/Linux, BSD, Solaris, Mac OS X ve Microsoft Windows için kullanılabilir, bir şahsî ve küçük iş mâlî muhâsebe yazılımı.
Size = 114,0 MiB

[Section.0425]
Description = Finantsarvestus tarkvara eraisikutele ja väikeettevõtjatele, tasuta litsentseeritud GNU GPL all ja saadaval GNU/Linux, BSD, Solaris, Mac OS X ja Microsoft Windows platvormidel.
Size = 114,0 MiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Un programa de contabilidad personal y de PYMEs liberado bajo los términos de la GNU GPL. Está disponible para GNU/Linux, BSD, Solaris, Mac OS X y Microsoft Windows.

[Section.0804]
Description = 个人和小企业财务管理软件，以 GNU GPL 许可免费发行，可供 GNU/Linux、BSD、Solaris、Mac OS X 和 Microsoft Windows 使用。

[Section.10]
Description = Un software di contabilità finanziaria personale e per piccole imprese, concesso in licenza gratuita con licenza GNU GPL e disponibile per GNU/Linux, BSD, Solaris, Mac OS X e Microsoft Windows.

