[Section]
Name = IndiFTPD
Version = 1.0.9 Beta
License = GPL
Description = A standalone FTP server that functions as a single executable. It is designed for situations when a user does not want to install/configure a server on the system (or does not have permission to do so) and wants to quickly get a server running.
Size = 556.0 KiB
Category = 5
URLSite = http://www.dftpd.com/products.php#indiftpd
URLDownload = http://www.dftpd.com/files/IndiFTPD/1.0.9_beta/Windows/Intel/indiftpd.exe
SHA1 = 106b5c86c563ed4d4d1976014a8b2562281e5e2d
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 569344

[Section.0407]
Description = Eigenständiger FTP Server in einer einzigen Anwendung. Er wurde erstellt für Situationen, in denen ein Anwender keinen Server auf dem System installieren/konfigurieren möchte (oder nicht die Rechte dafür besitzt) und schnell einen Server lauffähig bekommen will.
Size = 556,0 KiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Un servidor FTP autónomo que funciona como un único ejecutable. Útil para situaciones en las que no se quiere/puede instalar un servidor en el sistema y se necesita tener algo rápido que lo supla en un momento.

[Section.10]
Description = Un server FTP autonomo che funziona come un singolo eseguibile. È progettato per le situazioni in cui un utente non desidera installare/configurare un server sul sistema (o non dispone dell'autorizzazione per farlo) e desidera far funzionare rapidamente un server.

[Section.0415]
Description = IndiFTPD to samodzielny serwer FTP składający sie z jednego pliku wykonywalnego. Zaprojektowany z myślą o użytkownikach, którzy nie chcą instalować / konfigurować serwera w systemie (lub nie mają uprawnień) i chcą szybko uruchomić serwer FTP.

[Section.0418]
Description = Server FTP de sine stătător, într-un singur executabil. Este adresat situațiilor în care nu este posibilă sau nu se dorește instalarea/configurarea unui server în sistem, însă este necesară obținerea rapidă a unui server funcțional.
Size = 556,0 Kio

[Section.0419]
Description = Отдельный FTP-сервер, который работает как единый исполняемый файл. Он предназначен для ситуаций, когда пользователь не хочет устанавливать/настраивать сервер в системе (или не имеет прав, чтобы это сделать), но хочет быстро поднять сервер.
Size = 556,0 КиБ

[Section.041f]
Version = 1.0.9 Beta
Description = Bir tek çalıştırılabilir dosyadan oluşan tek başına bir FTP sunucusudur. Bir kullanıcının, çabucak, çalışan bir sunucuya sahip olmak istediği ve sisteminde bir sunucu kurmak/yapılandırmak istemediği (veyâ bunu yapmaya izni olmadığı) durumlar için tasarlanmıştır.
Size = 556,0 KiB

[Section.0425]
Version = 1.0.9 Beeta
Description = Iseseisev FTP server, mis funktsioneerib ühe ainsa rakendusena. See on disainitud olukordade jaoks, kus kasutaja ei soovi installida ega konfigureerida serverit süsteemil (või pole õiguseid selle jaoks) ja tahab kiirelt serveri tööle saada.
Size = 556,0 KiB

[Section.0804]
Description = 单可执行文件的独立 FTP 服务器。它被设计成适用于用户不想在系统上安装或配置服务器（或者没有权限这么做）并且想马上运行一个服务器的情况。

