[Section]
Name = KompoZer
Version = 0.7.10
License = MPL
Description = A complete web authoring system that combines web file management and easy-to-use WYSIWYG web page editing. You will need a ZIP decompression program to run it.
Size = 7.6 MiB
Category = 5
URLSite = http://www.kompozer.net/
URLDownload = http://download.sourceforge.net/project/kompozer/current/0.7.10/kompozer-0.7.10-win32.zip
SHA1 = cb0fbb2f9d4a547131176158e9e7185ee525a8a3
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 7949158

[Section.0a]
Description = Un completo sistema de autoría web que combina la gestión de archivos web y una interfaz WYSIWYG fácil de usar en la edición web. Necesitarás descomprimirlo para usarlo.

[Section.0407]
Description = Ein vollständiges Web-Authoring-System, welches Web-Datei-Management und leicht zu bedienende WYSIWYG Web-Seite Bearbeitung verbindet. Ein Werkzeug wie 7-Zip ist zum extrahieren notwendig.
Size = 7,6 MiB

[Section.0415]
Description = Oprogramowanie do tworzenia stron internetowych, które łączy zarządzanie plikami stron internetowych i łatwą edycję stron za pomocą WYSIWYG. Do jego uruchomienia potrzebny jest program dekompresyjny ZIP.
Size = 7,6 MiB

[Section.0418]
Description = Sistem complet de autorizare web care combină gestiunea fișierelor web și modul de editare directă a paginilor. Este necesar un utilitar ca 7-Zip pentru a-l putea extrage.
Size = 7,6 Mio

[Section.0419]
Description = Визуальный HTML-редактор, основанный на Nvu. Одна из лучших бесплатных альтернатив Adobe CS3. Вам потребуется программа распаковки ZIP, чтобы запустить его.
Size = 7,6 МиБ

[Section.041f]
Description = Ağ kütük yönetimiyle kullanımı kolay WYSIWYG ağ sayfası düzenlemesini birleştiren eksiksiz bir ağ yazarlık dizgesidir. Çalıştırmak için bir ZIP çıkartma programı gerekir.
Size = 7,6 MiB

[Section.0804]
Description = 一套完整的结合网络文件管理和简单易用的所见即所得网页编辑的网络创作系统。您将需要一个 ZIP 解压缩程序来运行它。

[Section.10]
Description = Un sistema completo di web authoring che combina la gestione dei file web e l'editing di pagine web WYSIWYG di facile utilizzo. Avrai bisogno di un programma di decompressione ZIP per eseguirlo.

