[Section]
Name = Lazarus
Version = 2.0.6
License = modified LGPL, GPL
Description = A cross-platform IDE that lets you create Object Pascal programs. It uses the Free Pascal compiler to build your projects.
Size = 127 MiB
Category = 7
URLSite = http://www.lazarus.freepascal.org/
URLDownload = https://sourceforge.net/projects/lazarus/files/Lazarus%20Windows%2032%20bits/Lazarus%202.0.6/lazarus-2.0.6-fpc-3.0.4-win32.exe
SHA1 = 20f58dea4405c142340fb486c9710752f4838a5d
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 133997259

[Section.0407]
Description = Plattformunabhängige IDE, mit der man Pascal-Programme erstellen kann. Es verwendet den Free Pascal Compiler um die Programme zu erzeugen.

[Section.0a]
Description = Un IDE multiplataforma para la creación de programas en Object Pascal. Utiliza el compilador Free Pascal para compilar los proyectos.

[Section.0415]
Description = Wielopratformowe zintegrowane środowisko programistyczne (IDE) które pozwala na tworzenie graficznych (GUI) i niegraficznych (działających w konsoli) programów obiektowych w języku Pascal. Program używa darmowego kompilatora Free Pascal.

[Section.10]
Description = Un IDE multipiattaforma che consente di creare programmi Object Pascal. Usa il compilatore Free Pascal per costruire i tuoi progetti.

[Section.0418]
License = GPL, LGPL modificată
Description = Mediu integrat de dezvoltare (IDE) multiplatformă care vă permite crearea de programe Object Pascal. Pentru compilarea proiectelor este utilizat compilatorul Free Pascal.
Size = 127 Mio

[Section.0419]
License = Измененная LGPL, GPL
Description = Открытая среда разработки программного обеспечения на языке Object Pascal для компилятора Free Pascal.
Size = 127 МиБ

[Section.041f]
License = Değiştirilmiş LGPL, GPL
Description = Object Pascal programları oluşturmanızı sağlayan çapraz platform bir IDE. Tasarılarınızı derlemek için Free Pascal derleyicisini kullanır.
Size = 127 MiB

[Section.0804]
Description = 允许您创建 Object Pascal 程序的跨平台 IDE。它使用 Free Pascal 语言编译器来构造您的项目。

