[Section]
Name = Miranda IM
Version = 0.10.21
License = GPL
Description = Open source multiprotocol instant messaging application. May not work completely.
Size = 2.8 MiB
Category = 5
URLSite = http://www.miranda-im.org/
URLDownload = https://web.archive.org/web/20140327190905if_/http://files.miranda-im.org/stable/0.10.21.0/miranda-im-v0.10.21-unicode.exe
SHA1 = 8b76ecba6e54abe99cc52b2f7c3c27726befaf0c
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 2951752

[Section.0407]
Description = Quelloffene Multiprotokoll Instant Messaging Anwendung. Funktioniert möglicherweise nicht vollständig.
Size = 2,8 MiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Aplicación de mensajería instantánea multiprotocolo de código abierto. Puede que no funcione del todo bien.

[Section.040c]
Description = Application de messagerie instantannée multi-protocoles open source - pourrait ne pas fonctionner complètement.
Size = 2,8 Mio

[Section.10]
Description = Applicazione di messaggistica istantanea multiprotocollo open source. Potrebbe non funzionare completamente.

[Section.0413]
Description = Open-bron multi-protocol instant message toepassing - werkt mogelijk niet volledig.

[Section.0415]
Description = Otwarty komunikator internetowy, obsługujący wiele różnych protokołów (m.in. GG, Tlen, Jabber, ICQ, IRC) - może nie działać prawidłowo.

[Section.0418]
Description = Aplicație de mesagerie instant multiprotocol (cu surse deschise). Este posibil să întâmpinați limitări de funcționalitate.
Size = 2,8 Mio

[Section.0419]
Description = Мультипротокольное приложение для обмена мгновенными сообщениями с открытым исходным кодом.
Size = 2,8 МиБ

[Section.041f]
Description = Açık kaynak, çoklu iletişim özellikli, anlık iletileşme uygulaması. Eksiksiz olarak çalışmayabilir.
Size = 2,8 MiB

[Section.0422]
Description = Відкрита мультипротокольна програма миттєвих повідомлень - може не працювати повністю.

[Section.0804]
Description = 开源的多协议即时通信应用程序。可能不会完全正常工作。

[Section.0813]
Description = Open-bron multi-protocol instant message toepassing - werkt mogelijk niet volledig.

