[Section]
Name = Neverball
Version = 1.6.0
License = GPLv2
Description = Tilt the floor to roll a ball through an obstacle course before time runs out. Neverball is part puzzle game, part action game, and entirely a test of skill. A tool like 7-Zip is needed for extracting the game.
Size = 72.3 MiB
Category = 4
URLSite = http://neverball.org/
URLDownload = http://neverball.org/neverball-1.6.0.zip
SHA1 = 51b744f87ee8c435959da1fa0b35472fe02c719b
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 75802818

[Section.0407]
Description = Neigen Sie den Boden, um einen Ball durch einen Hindernisparcours zu rollen, bevor die Zeit abläuft. Neverball ist teils ein Puzzle-Spiel, teils ein Action-Spiel und ganz ein Test der Geschicklichkeit. Zum extrahieren wird 7-Zip oder ähnlich benötigt.
Size = 72,3 MiB

[Section.0415]
Description = Przechyl podłogę, aby przetoczyć piłkę przez tor przeszkód, zanim skończy się czas. Neverball to gra akcji z elementami logicznymi, która sprawdzi twoje umiejętności. Do wypakowania gry potrzebne jest narzędzie typu 7-Zip.
Size = 72,3 MiB

[Section.0418]
Description = Joc în parte de tip enigmă, în parte de tip acțiune, și un test de aptitudine per total. Este necesar un utilitar ca 7-Zip pentru a-l putea extrage.
Size = 72,3 Mio

[Section.0419]
Description = Компьютерная игра-платформер, в которой игрок управляет мячом путём наклона опорной конструкции в трёхмерном пространстве. Для перехода на следующий уровень нужно открыть цель, собрав для этого определённое количество монет (очков), и попасть в неё мячом.
Size = 72,3 МиБ

[Section.0a]
Description = Gira el suelo para mover una bola a través de una pista de obstáculos a contra reloj. Neverball es mitad puzle, mitad juego de acción y toda una prueba de habilidad. Se necesita una herramienta como 7-Zip para extraer el juego.

[Section.041f]
License = GPL sürüm 2
Description = Süre bitmeden önce bir engel gidişi boyunca bir topu yuvarlamak için odayı eğiniz. Neverball, tikelik bulmaca oyunu, tikelik devingen oyun ve büsbütün bir ustalık sınamasıdır. Oyunu çıkartmak için 7-Zip benzeri bir araç gereklidir.
Size = 72,3 MiB

[Section.0804]
Description = 倾斜地板来使小球在规定时间内绕过障碍物。Neverball 一款是半解密半动作游戏，也是一种对技巧的考验。您将需要一个类似 7-Zip 的工具来提取游戏。

[Section.10]
Description = Inclina il pavimento per far rotolare una palla attraverso un percorso ad ostacoli prima che scada il tempo. Neverball è in parte un gioco di puzzle, in parte un gioco d'azione e interamente una prova di abilità. Uno strumento come 7-Zip è necessario per estrarre il gioco.

