[Section]
Name = Opera
Version = 12.18
License = Freeware
Description = The popular Opera Browser with many advanced features, including an e-mail and BitTorrent client.
Size = 12.4 MiB
Category = 5
URLSite = http://www.opera.com/
URLDownload = http://ftp.opera.com/pub/opera/win/1218/int/Opera_1218_int_Setup.exe
SHA1 = b2344bfd13e85dab4f50c0b579b9a485bf473136
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 12956472

[Section.0405]
Description = Populární prohlížeč Opera s mnoha pokročilými vlastnostmi, včetně vestavené podpory pro e-mail a BitTorrent.

[Section.0407]
Description = Der populäre Opera Browser mit vielen fortschrittlichen Eigenschaften, enthält einen E-Mail und BitTorrent Client.
Size = 12,4 MiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Popular navegador web con muchas características avanzadas, incluyendo un cliente de correo y BitTorrent.

[Section.040c]
Description = Le populaire navigateur Opera avec beaucoup de fonctionnalités avancées, incluant un client mail et BitTorrent.
Size = 12,4 Mio

[Section.10]
Description = Il popolare browser Opera con molte funzionalità avanzate, tra cui un client di posta elettronica e BitTorrent.

[Section.0413]
Description = De populaire Opera Browser met vele gevorderde mogelijkheden, inclusief e-mail en BitTorrent afnemers.

[Section.0415]
Description = Popularna przeglądarka internetowa z wieloma zaawansowanymi funkcjami, zawierająca klientów: poczty oraz BitTorrent.

[Section.0418]
License = Gratuită
Description = Navigator web popular cu multe funcționalități avansate, inclusiv un client de poștă electronică și de BitTorrent.
Size = 12,4 Mio

[Section.0419]
License = Бесплатно
Description = Популярный браузер со многими дополнительными возможностями, включающий клиентов почты и BitTorrent.
Size = 12,4 МиБ

[Section.041f]
License = Ücretsiz
Description = Bir posta ve BitTorrent istemcisini kapsayan birçok gelişmiş özellikle tutulan Opera Tarayıcı.
Size = 12,4 MiB

[Section.0422]
Description = Популярний браузер з багатьма додатковими можливостями, який включає в себе поштовий та BitTorrent клієнти.

[Section.0804]
License = 免费软件
Description = 流行的 Opera 浏览器，带有许多高级功能，包含电子邮件和 BitTorrent 客户端。

[Section.0813]
Description = De populaire Opera Browser met vele gevorderde mogelijkheden, inclusief e-mail en BitTorrent afnemers.

