[Section]
Name = Opera
Version = 9.64
License = Freeware
Description = The popular Opera Browser with many advanced features, including an e-mail and BitTorrent client.
Size = 7.2 MiB
Category = 5
URLSite = http://www.opera.com/
URLDownload = https://web.archive.org/web/20140327183619if_/http://arc.opera.com/pub/opera/win/964/int/Opera_964_int_Setup.exe
SHA1 = e7354e79956acae6f76727a3c9bb3c25ea3a7b6f
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 7562568

[Section.0405]
Description = Populární prohlížeč Opera s mnoha pokročilými vlastnostmi, včetně vestavené podpory pro e-mail a BitTorrent.

[Section.0407]
Description = Der populäre Opera Browser mit vielen fortschrittlichen Eigenschaften, enthält einen E-Mail und BitTorrent Client.
Size = 7,2 MiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Popular navegador web con muchas características avanzadas, incluyendo un cliente de correo y BitTorrent.

[Section.040c]
Description = Le populaire navigateur Opera avec beaucoup de fonctionnalités avancées, incluant un client mail et BitTorrent.
Size = 7,2 Mio

[Section.10]
Description = Il popolare browser Opera con molte funzionalità avanzate, tra cui un client di posta elettronica e BitTorrent.

[Section.0413]
Description = De populaire Opera Browser met vele gevorderde mogelijkheden, inclusief e-mail en BitTorrent afnemers.

[Section.0415]
Description = Popularna przeglądarka internetowa z wieloma zaawansowanymi funkcjami, zawierająca klientów: poczty oraz BitTorrent.

[Section.0418]
License = Gratuită
Description = Navigator popular cu multe funcționalități avansate, incluzând poștă electronică și client de BitTorrent.
Size = 7,2 Mio

[Section.0419]
License = Бесплатно
Description = Популярный браузер со многими дополнительными возможностями, включающий клиентов почты и BitTorrent.
Size = 7,2 МиБ

[Section.041f]
License = Ücretsiz
Description = Bir posta ve BitTorrent istemcisini kapsayan birçok gelişmiş özellikle tutulan Opera Tarayıcı.
Size = 7,2 MiB

[Section.0422]
Description = Популярний браузер з багатьма додатковими можливостями, який включає в себе поштовий та BitTorrent клієнти.

[Section.0804]
License = 免费软件
Description = 流行的 Opera 浏览器，带有许多高级功能，包含电子邮件和 BitTorrent 客户端。

[Section.0813]
Description = De populaire Opera Browser met vele gevorderde mogelijkheden, inclusief e-mail en BitTorrent afnemers.

