[Section]
Name = PDFsam Basic
Version = 3.3.5
License = GPLv2
Description = A free, open source, platform independent tool designed to perform split, merge and other manipulations on pdf document. Java Runtime needed!
Size = 14.7 MiB
Category = 6
URLSite = http://www.pdfsam.org/
URLDownload = https://download.sourceforge.net/project/pdfsam/pdfsam/3.3.5/pdfsam-v3.3.5.msi
SHA1 = 3baf154bf6ce75d62746d866fc5106c4c8300776
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 15396864

[Section.0a]
Description = Una herramienta de código abierto independiente, que divide, combina y edita otras funciones en un documento PDF. Necesita tener instalado Java runtime.

[Section.0407]
Description = Freies, quelloffenes, Plattformunabhängiges Werkzeug zum spiltten, zusammenfügen und anderer Manipulationen an PDF Dokumenten. Java Runtime benötigt!
Size = 14,7 MiB

[Section.0415]
Description = Darmowe, otwartoźródłowe wieloplatformowe narzędzie służące do dzielenia, scalania i innych operacji na dokumencie PDF. Wymagane jest środowisko uruchomieniowe Java!

[Section.0418]
Description = Instrument gratuit, cu surse deschise, multiplatformă, pentru împărțirea, unirea, și manipularea documentelor PDF. Este necesară Java Runtime!
Size = 14,7 Mio

[Section.0419]
Description = Инструмент, предназначенный для выполнения разделения, слияния и других операций с документами PDF.
Size = 14,7 МиБ

[Section.041f]
License = GPL sürüm 2
Description = PDF belgesi üzerinde bölme, birleştirme ve başka oynamalar yapmak için tasarlanmış, ücretsiz, açık kaynak, platform bağımsız bir araç. Java Yürütücüsü gereklidir!
Size = 14,7 MiB

[Section.0804]
Description = 一款免费、开源和平台独立的用于对 PDF 文档进行拆分、合并及其他操作的工具。需要 Java 运行库。

[Section.10]
Description = Uno strumento gratuito, open source e indipendente dalla piattaforma progettato per eseguire la divisione, l'unione e altre manipolazioni su documenti PDF. Java Runtime necessario!

