[Section]
Name = Pengupop
Version = 2.2.3
License = GPL
Description = The purpose of this game is to shoot colored orbs into your playfield, so they form groups of three or more.
Size = 1.7 MiB
Category = 4
URLDownload = http://svn.reactos.org/packages/Pengupop.exe
SHA1 = 59b87b20244cf13136f59c31b962a0521486a359
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 1780574

[Section.0407]
Description = Das Ziel des Spiels ist es farbige Orbs ins Spielfeld zu feuern, so dass diese Gruppen von drei oder mehr bilden.
Size = 1,7 MiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Dispara orbes de colores en el campo de juego formando grupos de más de tres.

[Section.10]
Description = Lo scopo di questo gioco è sparare sfere colorate nel tuo campo di gioco, in modo che formino gruppi di tre o più.

[Section.0415]
Description = Celem tej gry jest strzelanie kolorowymi kulkami tak, aby utworzyć rzędy trzech lub więcej kulek w tym samym kolorze.

[Section.0418]
Description = Scopul acestui joc este de a arunca globuri colorate în propriul teren pentru a forma grupuri de câte trei sau mai multe.
Size = 1,7 Mio

[Section.0419]
Description = Цель данной игры - стрелять цветными шариками в игровое поле, чтобы они образовывали группы из трех или более шариков.
Size = 1,7 МиБ

[Section.041f]
Description = Bu oyunun amacı, oyun alanınızda üç ya da daha çok takımdan oluşan renkli küreleri vurmaktır.
Size = 1,7 MiB

[Section.0804]
Description = 游戏的目的是将彩色弹珠发射到游戏台上，它们可以以三个或更多组成组。

