[Section]
Name = Precise Calculator
Version = 2.6.3
License = GPLv3
Description = A free and open source scientific calculator for Windows. You will need a ZIP decompression program to install it.
Size = 181.7 KiB
Category = 11
URLSite = http://preccalc.sourceforge.net
URLDownload = http://download.sourceforge.net/preccalc/preccalc-32bit.zip
SHA1 = 8877a4b8c9ac90db8256681c6c5b4583d9610c31
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 186050

[Section.0407]
Description = Freier und quelloffener wissenschaftlicher Rechner für Windows. Zum extrahieren wird 7-Zip oder ein ähnliches Tool benötigt.
Size = 181,7 KiB

[Section.0415]
Description = Darmowy i otwartoźródłowy kalkulator naukowy dla systemu Windows. Do instalacji wymagany jest program dekompresyjny ZIP.

[Section.0418]
Description = Calculatr științific gratuit, cu surse deschise. Este necesar un utilitar ca 7-Zip pentru a-l putea extrage.
Size = 181,7 Kio

[Section.0419]
Description = Бесплатный научный калькулятор с исходным кодом для Windows. Вам потребуется программа распаковки zip для установки.
Size = 181,7 КиБ

[Section.0a]
Description = Una calculadora científica gratuita y de código abierto. Es necesario un descompresor de archivos zip para abrirlo.

[Section.041f]
Name = Precise Hesap Makinesi
License = GPL sürüm 3
Description = Windows için özgür ve açık kaynak bir bilimsel hesap makinesidir. Kurmak için bir ZIP çıkartma izlencesi gerekir.
Size = 181,7 KiB

[Section.0804]
Description = 一个 Windows 上的免费开源科学计算器。你将需要一个 ZIP 解压缩程序来安装它。

[Section.10]
Description = Una calcolatrice scientifica gratuita e open source per Windows. Avrai bisogno di un programma di decompressione ZIP per installarlo.

