[Section]
Name = QB64 (SDL version)
Version = 1.2
License = Freeware
Description = A self-hosting BASIC compiler for Microsoft Windows, Linux and Mac OS X, designed to be compatible with Microsoft QBasic and Microsoft QuickBASIC. You will need a tool like 7-Zip to extract it.
Size = 98.0 MiB
Category = 7
URLSite = http://www.qb64.net/
URLDownload = https://web.archive.org/web/20180526110545if_/http://www.qb64.net/release/dirty/2018_05_19__05_07_33-1.2-20180202.85/windows/qb64-1.2-20180202.85-win.zip
SHA1 = 64b8f8d32c24c65598f9d655506fec25c4fb4052
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 102775452

[Section.0407]
Description = Self-Hosting BASIC-Compiler für Microsoft Windows, Linux und Mac OS X, entwickelt, um mit Microsoft QBasic und Microsoft QuickBASIC kompatibel zu sein. Sie müssen 7-Zip oder ein ähnliches Dienstprogramm installiert haben, um es zu extrahieren.
Size = 98,0 MiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Es un compilador auto-compilable de BASIC para Windows, Linux y Mac OS X, diseñado para ser compatible con Microsoft QuickBasic. Es necesario utilizar algo como 7-Zip para descomprimirlo.

[Section.10]
Description = Un compilatore BASIC self-hosting per Microsoft Windows, Linux e Mac OS X, progettato per essere compatibile con Microsoft QBasic e Microsoft QuickBASIC. Avrai bisogno di uno strumento come 7-Zip per estrarlo.

[Section.0415]
Description = QB64 to kompilator BASIC zdolny do kompilacji własnego kodu źródłowego. Działa w systemach Windows, Linux i Mac OS X. Jest kompatybilny z Microsoft QBasic i QuickBASIC. Wymaga programu archiwizującego do wypakowania.

[Section.0418]
License = Gratuită
Description = Compilator BASIC auto-compilabil pentru Windows, Linux și Mac OS X, conceput pentru a fi compatibil cu Microsoft QBasic și Microsoft QuickBASIC. Este necesar un utilitar de derarhivare de tip ZIP.
Size = 98,0 Mio

[Section.0419]
Name = QB64 (SDL версия)
License = Бесплатно
Description = Компилятор языка BASIC для Microsoft Windows, Linux и Mac OS X. Совместим с Microsoft QBasic и Microsoft QuickBASIC. Вам понадобится такой инструмент, как 7-zip, чтобы распаковать его.
Size = 98,0 МиБ

[Section.041f]
Name = QB64 (SDL sürümü)
License = Ücretsiz
Description = Microsoft Windows, Linux ve Mac OS X için, Microsoft QBasic ve Microsoft QuickBASIC ile uyumlu olacak biçimde tasarlanmış, kendi kendini derleyen bir BASIC derleyicisidir. Çıkartmak için 7-Zip benzeri bir araca gereksinim duyacaksınız.
Size = 98,0 MiB

[Section.0804]
License = 免费软件
Description = Microsoft Windows, Linux 及 Mac OS X 平台上的自托管 BASIC 编译器，设计上兼容 Microsoft QBasic 和 Microsoft QuickBASIC。您将需要一个像 7-Zip 的工具来解压它。

