[Section]
Name = ReactOS Build Environment
Version = 2.1.6
License = GPL
Description = Allows you to build the ReactOS source. For more instructions see ReactOS wiki.
Size = 35.6 MiB
Category = 7
URLSite = http://reactos.org/wiki/Build_Environment
URLDownload = https://download.sourceforge.net/reactos/RosBE-2.1.6.exe
SHA1 = 01b195f442cea01bcf21536f1c2e5d898ba9fe0c
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 37300572

[Section.0405]
Description = Dovoluje zkompilovat zdrojový kód systému ReactOS. Pro další detaily viz. ReactOS wiki.

[Section.0407]
Description = Erlaubt es Ihnen den ReactOS Source Code zu kompilieren. Im ReactOS-Wiki finden Sie dazu nähere Anweisungen.
Size = 35,6 MiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Te permite compilar el código de ReactOS. Para más información consulta la Wiki de ReactOS.

[Section.040c]
Description = Vous permet de compiler le code source de ReactOS. Pour plus d'instructions, reportez-vous au wiki ReactOS.
Size = 35,6 Mio

[Section.10]
Description = Permette di compilare i sorgenti di ReactOS. Per maggiori informazioni consultare il Wiki di ReactOS.

[Section.0413]
Description = Maakt het mogelijk om de ReactOS broncode te bouwen. Meer instructies vind u op de ReastOS wiki.

[Section.0415]
Description = Pozwala zbudować obraz płyty ReactOS ze źródeł. Więcej informacji na Wiki ReactOS.

[Section.0418]
Description = Permite compilarea surselor ReactOS. Pentru instrucțiuni, consultați wiki ReactOS.
Size = 35,6 Mio

[Section.0419]
Description = Позволит Вам собрать ReactOS из исходных кодов. Подробности смотрите в ReactOS wiki.
Size = 35,6 МиБ

[Section.041f]
Description = ReactOS kaynak kodlarını derlemenize olanak sağlar. Daha çok açıklama için ReactOS wikiye bakınız.
Size = 35,6 MiB

[Section.0422]
Description = Дозволяє зібрати ReactOS з вихідних кодів. За детальною інформацією дивіться в ReactOS Вікі.

[Section.0804]
Description = 可以让您编译 ReactOS 源码。更多的介绍请参阅 ReactOS wiki。

[Section.0813]
Description = Maakt het mogelijk om de ReactOS broncode te bouwen. Meer instructies vind u op de ReastOS wiki.

