[Section]
Name = SciTE
Version = 4.0.5
License = Freeware
Description = A SCIntilla based text editor. Originally built to demonstrate Scintilla, it has grown to be a generally useful editor with facilities for building and running programs.
Size = 3.3 MiB
Category = 7
URLSite = http://www.scintilla.org/
URLDownload = https://www.ebswift.com/uploads/7/0/4/0/70403747/scite-4.0.5x86.msi
SHA1 = bb2fc084824157912b1709352e8e3b6e3c6e4b25
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 3448832

[Section.0407]
Description = SCIntilla basierter Text Editor. Ursprünglich wurde er erstellt, um Scintilla vorzuführen, wuchs aber zu einem nützlichen Editor mit der Fähigkeit Programme zu erstellen und auszuführen.
Size = 3,3 MiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Editor de texto basado en SCIntilla. Originalmente creado para demostrar Scintilla, ha terminado siendo un gran editor con capacidad para crear y ejecutar programas.

[Section.040c]
Description = SciTE est un éditeur de texte basé sur SCIntilla. Originelement réalisé pour montrer Scintilla, il a évolué pour devenir un éditeur généralement utile avec des options pour compiler et lancer des programmes.
Size = 3,3 Mio

[Section.10]
Description = Un editor di testo basato su SCIntilla. Creato originariamente per dimostrare Scintilla, è diventato un editor generalmente utile con funzionalità per la creazione e l'esecuzione di programmi.

[Section.0413]
Description = SciTE is een tekstbewerker gebaseerd op SCIntilla. Origineel bedoeld om Scontilla te demonstreren, is uitgegroeid tot een handige editor met mogelijkheden voor ontwerken en uitvoeren van programma's.

[Section.0415]
Description = SciTE to edytor tekstu bazowany na SCIntilla. Oryginalnie stworzony aby pokazać Scintille, stał sie ogólnie przydatnym edytorem z infrastrukturą potrzebną do tworzenia i uruchamiania programów.

[Section.0418]
License = Gratuită
Description = Editor de text bazat pe SCIntilla. Construit inițial pentru a demonstra Scintilla, a crescut ulterior într-un editor de uz general cu funcționalități de compilare și execuție a programelor.
Size = 3,3 Mio

[Section.0419]
License = Бесплатно
Description = Кроссплатформенный текстовый редактор.
Size = 3,3 МиБ

[Section.041f]
License = Ücretsiz
Description = Bir Scintilla tabanlı metin düzenleyicisidir. İlk başta Scintilla'yı göstermek için yapıldı; programları yapmak ve çalıştırmak yetenekleriyle, özellikle kullanışlı bir düzenleyici olmak için gelişti.
Size = 3,3 MiB

[Section.0422]
Description = Текстовий редактор на основі SCIntilla. Був зібраний як презентація Scintilla, але виріс до редактора загального користування з засобами збирання та запуску програм.

[Section.0804]
License = 免费软件
Description = 一个基于 SCIntilla 的文本编辑器。最初构建用于证明 Scintilla，现在已经发展成能够构造并运行程序的可用的编辑器。

[Section.0813]
Description = SciTE is een tekstbewerker gebaseerd op SCIntilla. Origineel bedoeld om Scontilla te demonstreren, is uitgegroeid tot een handige editor met mogelijkheden voor ontwerken en uitvoeren van programma's.

