[Section]
Name = ScummVM
Version = 2.0.0
License = GPL
Description = Open source reimplementation of classic adventure videogame engines (like Monkey Island, Sam and Max or Day of the Tentacle), making them work on ReactOS.
Size = 11.4 MiB
Category = 4
URLSite = http://scummvm.org/
URLDownload = https://scummvm.org/frs/scummvm/2.0.0/scummvm-2.0.0-win32.exe
SHA1 = df72f47edc1341dae439815fdaf4c857feae5924
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 11985315

[Section.0407]
Description = Quelloffene Implementierung von klassischen Abenteuervideospiel-Engines (wie Monkey Island, Sam and Max oder Day of the Tentacle), so dass sie auf ReactOS funktionieren.
Size = 11,4 MiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Reimplementación de código abierto de motores de juegos de aventura clásicos (como «Monkey Island», «Sam and Max» o «Day of the Tentacle»), haciéndolos funcionar en ReactOS.

[Section.040c]
Description = Sam and Max, Day of the Tentacle, etc sur ReactOS.
Size = 11,4 Mio

[Section.10]
Description = Reimplementazione open source dei classici motori di videogiochi d'avventura (come Monkey Island, Sam e Max o Day of the Tentacle), facendoli funzionare su ReactOS.

[Section.0413]
Description = Sam and Max, Day of the Tentacle, enz. op ReactOS.

[Section.0415]
Description = Program pozwalający uruchomić stare gry przygodowe (Sam and Max, Day of the Tentacle, Monkey Island) w ReactOS.

[Section.0418]
Description = Reimplementarea în surse deschise a motoarelor clasice de jocuri video de aventură (ca „Monkey Island”, „Sam and Max”, sau „Day of the Tentacle”), făcându-le să meargă în ReactOS.
Size = 11,4 Mio

[Section.0419]
Description = Коллекция игровых движков, созданных заново (независимо от разработчиков оригиналов), таких игр, как:  Monkey Island, Sam and Max или Day of the Tentacle, заставляя их работать в ReactOS.
Size = 11,4 МиБ

[Section.041f]
Description = Sam ve Max, Day of the Tentacle, Monkey Island gibi klasik mâcera video oyunlarının oyun motorlarının ReactOS üzerinde çalışmasını sağlayan açık kaynak uyarlaması.
Size = 11,4 MiB

[Section.0422]
Description = Дозволить грати Sam and Max, Day of the Tentacle та інші класичні ігри в ReactOS.

[Section.0804]
Description = 经典冒险游戏引擎(如 Monkey Island, Sam and Max 及 Day of the Tentacle)的开源复刻，使他们能运行在 ReactOS 上。

[Section.0813]
Description = Sam and Max, Day of the Tentacle, enz. op ReactOS.

