[Section]
Name = Simple Direct Media Layer (SDL) Runtime
Version = 1.2.15
License = LGPL
Description = Needed for many open source games to run. You will need a tool like 7-Zip to extract it.
Size = 136.7 KiB
Category = 14
URLSite = http://www.libsdl.org/
URLDownload = http://www.libsdl.org/release/SDL-1.2.15-win32.zip
SHA1 = 84a5c93097bef703bc74ff5eb5c4943fda449629
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 139948

[Section.0405]
Description = Nutný pro spuštění některých open source her. K rozbalení je nutný 7-zip nebo podobný nástroj.

[Section.0407]
Description = Erforderlich um einige quelloffene Spiele auszuführen. Sie brauchen 7-Zip oder einen ähnlichen Entpacker um es zu entpacken.
Size = 136,7 KiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Necesario para ejecutar muchos juegos de código abierto. Se necesita 7-Zip o una utilidad similar para extraerlo.

[Section.040c]
Name = Bibliothèque Simple Direct Media Layer (SDL)
Description = Nécessaire pour faire tourner certains jeux open source. Vous aurez besoin de 7-Zip ou d'un outil similaire pour l'extraire.
Size = 136,7 Kio

[Section.10]
Description = Necessario per l'esecuzione di molti giochi open source. Avrai bisogno di uno strumento come 7-Zip per estrarlo.

[Section.0413]
Description = Gebruikt door veel open-bron-spelletjes. Gebruik 7-zip om het uit te pakken.

[Section.0415]
Name = Biblioteka uruchomieniowa Simple Direct Media Layer (SDL)
Description = Wymagana przez wiele gier (głównie o otwartym źródle). Do jej rozpakowania potrzebny jest program 7-Zip lub podobny.

[Section.0418]
Description = Necesar pentru execuția multor jocuri (cu surse deschise). Este necesar un utilitar ca 7-Zip pentru a-l putea extrage.
Size = 136,7 Kio

[Section.0419]
Description = Нужен для запуска многих игр с открытым исходным кодом. Вам понадобится такой инструмент, как 7-zip, чтобы распаковать его.
Size = 136,7 КиБ

[Section.041f]
Name = Simple Direct Media Layer (SDL) Yürütücü
Description = Birçok açık kaynak oyunu çalıştırmak için gereklidir. Çıkartmak için Zip gibi bir araca gereksinim duyacaksınız.
Size = 136,7 KiB

[Section.0422]
Name = Бібліотека Simple Direct Media Layer (SDL)
Description = Необхідна для роботи багатьох відкритих ігор. Вам потрібен 7-Zip або подібна утиліта щоб розпакувати її.

[Section.0804]
Description = 很多的开源游戏需要它才能够运行。您将需要一个像 7-Zip 的工具来解压它。

[Section.0813]
Description = Gebruikt door veel open-bron-spelletjes. Gebruik 7-zip om het uit te pakken.

