[Section]
Name = SNES9x
Version = 1.60
License = GPL
Description = A portable, freeware Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES) emulator. You'll need to change the video renderer to OpenGL in the video settings or in the ini file.
Size = 2.61 MiB
Category = 4
URLSite = https://github.com/snes9xgit/snes9x/
URLDownload = https://github.com/snes9xgit/snes9x/releases/download/1.60/snes9x-1.60-win32.zip
SHA1 = a67156f159405c73be86df49818f9984dfee218d
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 2619607

[Section.040c]
Description = Un émulateur portable et gratuit de Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES). Vous devrez utiliser OpenGL comme moteur de rendu dans les paramètres vidéo ou dans le fichier .ini.

[Section.0a]
Description = Un emulador de Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES) portátil y gratuito. Deberá cambiar el renderizador de video a OpenGL en la configuración de video o en el archivo ini.

[Section.10]
Description = Un emulatore di Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES) portatile e gratuito. Dovrai cambiare il renderer video in OpenGL nelle impostazioni video o nel file ini.

