[Section]
Name = Tile World
Version = 1.3.2
License = GPL
Description = Nice clone of Chip's Challenge originally made for the Atari Lynx. Includes free CCLP2 Graphics Pack, so you don't need the copyrighted original.
Size = 1.1 MiB
Category = 4
URLSite = http://www.muppetlabs.com/~breadbox/software/tworld/
URLDownload = http://www.muppetlabs.com/~breadbox/pub/software/tworld/tworld-1.3.2-win32.exe
SHA1 = d9d3b1c443cd4a31d48675e2bf2281dd4af48541
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 1195967

[Section.0407]
Description = Schöner Klon von Chip's Challenge ursprünglich etnwickelt für Atari Lynx. Enthält CCLP2 Graphics Pack, deshalb wird das urheberrechtlich geschützte Original nicht benötigt.
Size = 1,1 MiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Clon de «Chip's Challenge» creado originalmente para Atari Lynx. Incluye el paquete gráfico gratuito CCLP2, por lo que no es necesario tener los archivos originales.

[Section.040c]
Description = Clone sympathique de Chip's Challenge originelment fait pour Atari Lynx. Il inclut le pack de graphisme gratuit CCLP2, ainsi vous n'avez pas besoin de l'original sous copyrigth.
Size = 1,1 Mio

[Section.10]
Description = Simpatico clone di Chip's Challenge originariamente realizzato per l'Atari Lynx. Include il pacchetto grafico CCLP2 gratuito, quindi non è necessario l'originale protetto da copyright.

[Section.0413]
Description = Kloon van Chip's Challenge origineel gemaakt voor de Atari Lynx. Bevat het gratis CCLP2 Graphics Pack, zodat je zonder het origineel kan, dat onder auteursrecht valt.

[Section.0415]
Description = Udany klon gry Chip's Challenge z Atari Lynx. Zawiera darmowy zestaw grafik CCLP2.

[Section.0418]
Description = Clonă a jocului „Chip's Challenge”, creată inițial pentru Atari Lynx. Este inclus și pachetul gratuit CCLP2 Graphics, deci nu este necesar jocul original cu drepturi de autor.
Size = 1,1 Mio

[Section.0419]
Description = Головоломка. GPL Клон Chip's Challenge
Size = 1,1 МиБ

[Section.041f]
Description = Başlangıçta Atari Lynx için yapılan Chip's Challenge oyununun iyi bir taklidi. Ücretsiz CCLP2 Çizge Paketi'ni kapsar, bu yüzden telifli özgününe gereksinim duymazsınız.
Size = 1,1 MiB

[Section.0422]
Description = Чудовий клон гри Chip's Challenge для Atari Lynx. Включено безплатний графічний пакет CCLP2, тому вам не потрібен оригінальний.

[Section.0804]
Description = 曾用于 Atari Lynx 平台的 Chip's Challenge 的优秀的复刻版。已包含免费的 CCLP2 图形包，因此您不需要受版权保护的原版。

[Section.0813]
Description = Kloon van Chip's Challenge origineel gemaakt voor de Atari Lynx. Bevat het gratis CCLP2 Graphics Pack, zodat je zonder het origineel kan, dat onder auteursrecht valt.

