[Section]
Name = UltraISO
Version = 9.7.1.3519
License = Trial verison
Description = An ISO CD/DVD image file creating/editing/converting tool and a bootable CD/DVD maker, it can directly edit the CD/DVD image file and extract files and folders from it, as well as directly make ISO files from your CD/DVD-ROM or hard disk.
Size = 4.3 MiB
Category = 12
URLSite = https://www.ezbsystems.com/ultraiso/
URLDownload = https://web.archive.org/web/20180413051731if_/http://dw.ezbsys.net/uiso9_pe.exe
SHA1 = 2ea6f41e99886667a185608328c9adb03e6aa9ed
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 4536880

[Section.0415]
License = Wersja próbna
Description = Program do tworzenia, edycji, lub konwertowania obrazów płyt CD/DVD (bootowalnych i zwykłych). Można bezpośrednio edytować plik obrazu, wypakować z niego pliki i foldery, potrafi równierz utworzyć obrazy ISO z napędu optycznego lub plików na dysku twardym.

[Section.0418]
License = Versiune de evaluare
Description = Instrument pentru crearea/editarea/conversia fișierelor de tip imagine ISO CD/DVD. Permite editarea copierea fișierelor ISO de pe o unitate CD/DVD, extracția din asemenea fișiere, și editarea directă, inclusiv pentru medii de inițializare.
Size = 4,3 Mio

[Section.0419]
License = Пробная версия
Description = Программа для создания, редактирования и конвертирования различных форматов CD и DVD-образов.
Size = 4,3 МиБ

[Section.041f]
License = Deneme sürümü
Description = CD/DVD kalıp dosyasını doğrudan düzenleyebilmekle ve ondan dosyaları ve dizinleri çıkartabilmekle birlikte CD/DVD-ROM diskinizden ya da sâbit diskinizden doğrudan ISO dosyaları oluşturabilen bir ISO CD/DVD kalıp dosyası oluşturma, düzenleme, dönüştürme uygulaması ve bir ön yüklenebilir CD/DVD oluşturucusudur.
Size = 4,3 MiB

[Section.0804]
License = 试用版本
Description = 一款针对 ISO CD/DVD 镜像文件创建、编辑及转换的工具，它也可以用来制作可引导 CD/DVD。它可以直接编辑编辑 CD/DVD 的镜像文件并从中释放文件或目录，也可以直接从您的 CD/DVD-ROM 或硬盘中创建 ISO 文件。

[Section.0a]
Description = Una herramienta para crear, convertir y editar imágenes ISO, y un creador de CD/DVD, que puede editar directamente las imágenes de CD/DVD para extraer archivos o carpetas. Crea imágenes de disco duro y CD/DVD.

[Section.10]
Description = Uno strumento di creazione/modifica/conversione di file immagine ISO CD/DVD e un creatore di CD/DVD avviabile, può modificare direttamente il file immagine CD/DVD ed estrarre file e cartelle da esso, nonché creare direttamente file ISO dal CD/DVD-ROM o disco rigido.

