[Section]
Name = Winamp
Version = 5.666 Full
License = Freemium
Description = A media player that supports extensibility with plug-ins and skins, and features music visualization, playlist and a media library, supported by a large online community.
Size = 14.3 MiB
Category = 1
URLSite = http://www.winamp.com/
URLDownload = http://winamp.meggamusic.co.uk/winamp5666_full_all_redux.exe
SHA1 = 136314be0da42ed399b88a106cb1f43093e2c0c2
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 15023516

[Section.0407]
Description = Media Player welcher Erweiterbarkeit mit Plug-Ins und Skins ermöglicht und Musikvisualisierung, Playlist und Medienbibliothek bietet. Er wird durch eine große Online-Community unterstützt.
Size = 14,3 MiB

[Section.0415]
Description = Odtwarzacz multimedialny ze wsparciem dla rozszerzeń i skórek, oferujący takie funkcje jak wizualizacja muzyki, playlista i biblioteka, wspierany przez dużą społeczność internetową.

[Section.0418]
License = Gratuită, cu funcționalități opționale negratuite
Description = Lector media cu diverse extensii, având o largă comunitate de utilizatori.
Size = 14,3 Mio

[Section.0419]
License = Условно бесплатно
Description = Поддерживает расширяемость с помощью плагинов и скинов. Имеет возможность визуализировать музыку. Есть списки воспроизведения и медиа-библиотека.
Size = 14,3 МиБ

[Section.041f]
Version = 5.666 Eksiksiz
License = Ücretsiz Seçkin
Description = Winamp, eklentilerle ve dış görünümlerle genişletilebilirliği destekleyen, mûsikî sanallaştırmayı, çalma sistemini ve büyük bir çevrim içi topluluk tarafından desteklenen bir ortam kitaplığını barındıran bir ortam oynatıcısıdır.
Size = 14,3 MiB

[Section.0804]
License = 免费商业软件
Description = 一个支持插件、皮肤、音乐可视化功能、播放列表和媒体库媒体播放器，由一个大型的在线社区提供支持。

[Section.0a]
Description = Un reproductor de media que soporta una gran cantidad de plugins, skins y presenta visualización musical, listas, librería media, con soporte de una gran comunidad online.

[Section.10]
Description = Un lettore multimediale che supporta l'estensibilità con plug-in e skin e offre visualizzazione di musica, playlist e una libreria multimediale, supportata da una vasta comunità online.

