[Section]
Name = WinBoard
Version = 4.8.0
License = GPLv3
Description = A graphical chessboard for the Windows/ReactOS that can serve as a user interface for GNU Chess, Crafty, and other chess engines, for the Internet chess servers, and for electronic mail correspondence chess.
Size = 2.4 MiB
Category = 4
URLSite = http://hgm.nubati.net
URLDownload = http://hgm.nubati.net/WinBoard-4.8.0.exe
SHA1 = a242194b7582c196612f78b397bac892bb6908e0
CDPath = none
SizeBytes = 2551668

[Section.0407]
Description = Grafisches Schachbrett für Windows/ReactOS welches als Nutzerinterface für GNU Chess, Crafty oder andere Schachprogramme, für Internet Schachserver und für Briefschach dient.
Size = 2,4 MiB

[Section.0a]
Description = Tablero de ajedrez para Windows/ReactOS que puede ser utilizado como interfaz para GNU Chess, Crafty, y otros motores de ajedrez, para servidores de ajedrez en internet, así como para partidas por correo electrónico.

[Section.040c]
Description = WinBoard est un jeu d'échec graphique pour Windows/ReactOS qui peut servir d'interface utilisateur pour GNU Chess, Crafty et d'autres moteurs d'échecs, pour les serveurs d'échec internet et pour le jeu d'échec par courriel.
Size = 2,4 Mio

[Section.10]
Description = Una scacchiera grafica per Windows/ReactOS che può servire come interfaccia utente per GNU Chess, Crafty e altri motori scacchistici, per i server di scacchi Internet e per la corrispondenza di posta elettronica.

[Section.0413]
Description = WinBoard is een grafisch schaakbord voor Windows/ReactOS dat kan worden gebruikt als gebruikersinterface voor GNU Check, Crafty en andere schaakmotoren, voor Internet Chess Servers en voor schaak via elektronische post.

[Section.0415]
Description = Graficzna szachownica dla systemu Windows/ReactOS, która może służyć jako graficzna nakładka dla GNU Chess, Crafty, lub innych programów szachowych (w tym internetowych serwerów szachowych) lub szachów korespondencyjnych.

[Section.0418]
Description = WinBoard este o tablă de șah grafică pentru Windows/ReactOS ce poate servi ca interfață pentru GNU Chess, Crafty, sau alte motoare de șah, pentru servere de șah din Internet, sau pentru corespondență poștală de șah.
Size = 2,4 Mio

[Section.0419]
Description = Графическая шахматная доска для Windows/ReactOS, которая может служить интерфейсом пользователя для GNU Chess, Crafty и других шахматных движков, игровых интернет серверов, электронной почты, переписке в шахматы.
Size = 2,4 МиБ

[Section.041f]
License = GPL sürüm 3
Description = İnternet satranç sunucularına ve postayla yazışmalı satranca GNU Chess, Crafty ve başka satranç motorlarını bir kullanıcı arayüzü olarak sunabilen, Windows/ReactOS için bir çizgelik satranç tahtasıdır.
Size = 2,4 MiB

[Section.0422]
Description = Графічна шахматна дошка для Windows/ReactOS, що може слугувати графічним інтерфейсом для GNU Chess, Crafty, та інших шахматних двигунів, для серверів інтернет-шахмат та для шахматної переписки по е-мейл.

[Section.0804]
Description = 适用于 Windows/ReactOS 的图形化棋盘软件，能够作为 GNU Chess, Crafty 及其他棋类游戏引擎的用户界面，支持网络棋类游戏服务器及通过电邮下棋。

[Section.0813]
Description = WinBoard is een grafisch schaakbord voor Windows/ReactOS dat kan worden gebruikt als gebruikersinterface voor GNU Check, Crafty en andere schaakmotoren, voor Internet Chess Servers en voor schaak via elektronische post.

